{
    "id": "2b9827dafab040cfafb9cdc54b2b65b0",
    "title": "Prepositions of place exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ba900543864d417b9d5f7b303b4d532f",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can you see a woman ............................... the picture?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "London is ............................... the river Thames.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "above",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The man is sitting ................................. a table.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "in front of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The mother sat ................................ her children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beside",
                        "besides"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are a laptop and a few books ............................... the table.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He put the money ..................................... the box.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cat was hiding .................................. the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "behind",
                        "out",
                        "under"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why do you wear that ring ................................... your first finger?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you see the helicopter ..................................... the palace?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "above",
                        "over",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The plane was flying ................................. Scotland.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "through",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}